New York State Department of State Bureau of Miscellaneous Records Enrolled Acts of the State Legislature
New York State Archives
- Original Laws 1894 Chapters 428-614, 13036-78 (Volume 552)
- Original Laws 1894 Chapters 615-769, 13036-78 (Volume 553)
- Original Laws 1897 Chapter 378, 13036-78 (Volume 554)
- Vol. 234 Was Not Used, 13036-78 (Volume 234)
- Vol. 259 Was Not Used, 13036-78 (Volume 259)
- Vol. 357 Was Not Used, 13036-78 (Volume 357)
- Original Laws 1877 Code of Civil Procedures Standard Text, 13036-78 (Volume 466)
- Original Laws 1880 Chapters 1-95, 13036-78 (Volume 474)
- Original Laws 1979 Chapters 1-751, 13036-85 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1980 Chapters 1-904, 13036-85 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1981 Chapters 1-1061, 13036-85 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1982 Chapters 1-931, 13036-85 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1983 Chapters 1-1021, 13036-85 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1984 Chapters 1-560, 13036-85 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1984 Chapters 561-1018, 13036-85 (Box 7)
- Original Laws 1985 Chapters 1-500, 13036-88 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1985 Chapters 501-934, Line Vetoes 1-3, 13036-88 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1986 Chapters 1-450, 13036-88 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1986 Chapters 451-939, Line Vetoes 2-4, 13036-88 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1987 Chapters 1-450, 13036-88 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1987 Chapters 451-860, Line Veto 4, Veto 23, 13036-88 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1988 Chapters 1-240, 13036-89 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1988 Chapters 241-524, 13036-89 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1988 Chapters 525-794, 13036-89 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1989 Chapters 1-120, 13036-90 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1989 Chapters 121-349, 13036-90 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1989 Chapters 350-600, 13036-90 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1989 Chapters 601-779, 13036-90 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 1-120, 13036-91 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 121-300, 13036-91 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 301-520, 13036-91 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 521-720, 13036-91 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 721-920, 13036-91 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1990 Chapters 921-952, 13036-91 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1991 Chapters 1-9, 11-130, 13036-93 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1991 Chapters 131-340, 13036-93 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1991 Chapters 341-550, 13036-93 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1991 Chapters 551-750, 13036-93 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 1-100, 13036-93 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 101-300, 13036-93 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 301-500, 13036-93 (Box 7)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 501-670, 13036-93 (Box 8)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 671-800, 13036-93 (Box 9)
- Original Laws 1992 Chapters 801-858, 13036-93 (Box 10)
- Original Laws 1993 Chapters 1-100, 13036-94 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1993 Chapters 101-300, 13036-94 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1993 Chapters 301-500, 13036-94 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1993 Chapters 501-700, 13036-94 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1993 Chapters 701-731, 13036-94 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1994 Chapters 1-450, 13036-96 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1994 Chapters 451-738, 13036-96 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1995 Chapters 1-100, 13036-96 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1995 Chapters 101-400, 13036-96 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1995 Chapters 401-694, 13036-96 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1996 Chapters 1-200, 13036-99 (Box 1)
- Original Laws 1996 Chapters 201-400, 13036-99 (Box 2)
- Original Laws 1996 Chapters 401-606, 13036-99 (Box 3)
- Original Laws 1996 Chapters 607-731, 13036-99 (Box 4)
- Original Laws 1997 Chapters 1-150, 13036-99 (Box 5)
- Original Laws 1997 Chapters 151-350, 13036-99 (Box 6)
- Original Laws 1997 Chapters 351-500, 13036-99 (Box 7)
- Original Laws 1997 Chapters 501-687, 13036-99 (Box 8)
- Original Laws 1998 Chapters 1-86, 13036-99 (Box 9)
- Original Laws 1998 Chapters 87-225, 13036-99 (Box 10)
- Original Laws 1998 Chapters 226-500, 13036-99 (Box 11)
- Original Laws 1998 Chapters 501-657, 13036-99 (Box 12)